Suyeong Park

suyeong.park0@gmail.com | github.com/euphoria0-0

RESEARCH INTEREST

My research interests are mainly on making more **Trustworthy AI** tech using collaborations of information in data and knowledge from human beings. I believe 'understanding an intrinsic attributes of things using our knowledge' is crucial for deploying ML models for better human-being life in a real-world. Thus, I'm interested in identifying **Causality** of things from our data for reliable AI while overcoming the limitations of ML.

EDUCATION

Ulsan National Institute of Science and Technology (UNIST)

Ulsan, Korea

Master of Science in Artificial Intelligence

Aug. 2020 - Aug. 2022

GPA: 4.15/4.3

Advisor: Prof. Kwang In Kim and Prof. Namhoon Lee

Relevant Coursework: Causal Learning & Explainable AI, Reinforcement Learning, Advanced Machine Learning Topics

University of Seoul

Seoul, Korea

Bachelor of Science in Statistics and Data Science

Mar. 2015 - Feb. 2020

GPA: 3.7/4.5

Relevant Coursework: Bayesian Statistics, Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Time Series Analysis, Multivariate Statistics, Statistical Computing, Linear Algebra, Probability Theory, Mathematical Statistics

EXPERIENCE

Research Intern, Lunit	Jan. 2023 - Present
Bayesian Optimization for Hyperparameter tuning in AutoML team	$Seoul,\ Korea$
Visiting Researcher, CausalML Lab@Purdue University	Jul. 2022 - Aug. 2022
Bayesian Causal Discovery	West Lafayette, US
Research Assistant, $MLV \ Lab@UNIST$	Aug. 2020 - Aug. 2022
active learning, transfer learning, federated learning, image attribute estimation	$Ulsan,\ Korea$
Data Analyst and Engineer Intern, Seoul Big Data Campus	Mar. 2020 - Jun. 2020
Citizen Movement and Consumption Behaviour analysis around Seoul city	$Seoul,\ Korea$
Data Analyst Intern, FSC	Sep. 2019 - Feb. 2020
Data analysis with financial public data	Seoul, Korea

Publication

Active Deep Learning Guided by Efficient Gaussian Process Surrogates

preprint

S. Park*, Y. Ahn*, K. Kim., In Submission, 2022

Active Client Selection for Communication-efficient Federated Learning

 $|\underline{\text{link}}|$

S. Park, Master's Thesis, 2022

PROJECTS

Bayesian Optimization Hyperparameter tuning

Jan. 2023 - Present

Visual Common Sense Through Self-supervised Learning for Restoration of April. 2021 – Aug. 2022 Invisible Parts in Image

Causal Learning with Artificial Intelligence for genome dataset

Mar. 2021 - Dec. 2021

Citizen Movement and Consumption Behaviour analysis around Seoul city Apr. 2020 – Jun. 2020

Data analysis with financial public data

Jan. 2020 – Feb. 2020

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: Python, R, SQL

 $\textbf{Frameworks}: \ \underline{\text{PyTorch}}, \ \text{TensorFlow}, \ \text{Scipy}, \ \text{numpy}, \ \text{pandas}, \ \text{statsmodel}, \ \text{Matplotlib}, \ \text{seaborn}, \ \text{wandb}, \ \text{optuna}$

Others: Git, Docker, PyCharm, VSCode, QGIS, Tableau, SAS

Last Updated: January 14, 2023